searchgi.com 2013-04-04

# Create & Search Websites For Free - Searchgi.com

Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)   
• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)   
• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)   
• To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.   
• To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

#### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to facilitate monthly payment transactions only..

#### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

######  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

###### Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

###### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

###### Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.searchgi.com](http://www.searchgi.com/)

###### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

###### violation(s):

###### Issues:

\- Insufficient content

###### Further detail:

Insufficient content: Your pages need to have enough text on them for our specialists to review and to be able to determine what your pages are about.

###### To resolve this issue, please work through the following suggestions:

\- Make sure that your pages have sufficient text - websites that contain mostly images, videos or Flash animations will not be approved.

\- Your content should contain complete sentences and paragraphs, not only headlines.

\- Ensure that your website is fully built - do not publish while your site’s still in a beta or "under construction” phase or only consists of a website template.

\- Provide a clear navigation system for your visitors so that they can easily find all of the sections and pages of your website.

As soon as you've made the necessary changes, we’ll be happy to take another look at your account.

To update and resubmit your site(s), please sign in using the email address and password you submitted with your account. 

Our specialists will review your account for compliance with our program policies, so please make sure to resolve all of the issues listed above before resubmitting your site(s).

This policy was last modified on Feb 28th, 2013
